年轻的小龙们  在我们给落后的埃文
Young dragons, before we give the weak link
最后一次赢得蓝腰带
known as Evan his final chance
的机会之前
to earn his blue belt,
花几分钟来喂饱你们内心中的猛龙吧
take a few moments to feed your inner dragons.
拜托这是零食时间  配合我一下好不
It's snack time. Work with me here.
我本打算放弃他  开始找一个新死党
I was about to give up and look for a new sidekick
但当我想起有一次埃文只是因为他妈妈给了他
when I remembered the time Evan lost it
海苔片而严重暴走
because his mom gave him seaweed chips.
所以我就把他的生杏仁
So I swapped out his raw almonds
都换成了恶心的水草
for some of that disgusting water weed.
至少我们还能最后一次在一起吃零食啊
At least we get to have snack together one last time.
你准备好吃零食了么
Are you ready for your snack?
你也该吃零食了吧
You should have your snack.
- 我其实还没那么  - 我说了让你吃零食
- I'm not really that... - I said eat your snack.
我不敢相信啊
I can't believe this!
怎么了啊
What's wrong?
居然是海苔片
It's seaweed chips!
新鲜的  有机的  海苔片
Unsalted, organic, seaweed chips.
我一直跟我妈说我恨死海苔片了
I keep telling my mom I hate them.
给我萝卜条或者芹菜
Give me carrot sticks or celery
哪怕是高丽菜也好  偏偏是海苔片
or even rutabaga, just not seaweed chips!
得了吧  哥们
Come on, dude.
听妈妈的话把它吃掉咯
Listen to your mom and eat it!
打死我也不吃海苔
I won't eat seaweed!
怎么了  看什么看
What, what?!
我真是个好朋友啊
I'm a good friend.
谁还想尝尝我的厉害
Who else wants some?
小龙埃文  这就是你的龙气啊
Dragon Evan, that was your inner dragon.
它被释放出来了
It's been released!
你已经准备好系上蓝腰带了
You are ready for your blue belt now.
太棒了  埃文  你成功了
Yes! Evan, you did it.
你小子别跟我讲废话
Tell me something that I don't know.
别被我甩下了  小子
Try to keep up, munch.